thetopcoupon.com 2016-06-27

# Privacy Policy - The Top Coupon

#### Privacy Policy

get in touch

When you are using our website rest assured that we will be making every effort to protect your privacy. The following information outlines our privacy policy as it applies to The Top Coupon.

If you continue to use this site this means that you have understood our Privacy Policy and that you agree to the terms. Your use of this website also means that you accept our Terms and Conditions. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at the address provided at the bottom of the page.

What Information Do We Collect?

Certain information such as browser type, domain name and statistics for which pages and deals are being viewer are collected by this website automatically. This is known as “passive information” and is collected from all visitors in on an anonymous basis as you browse the website. It is collected using a standard internet technology known as “cookies”. Cookies are small pieces of data which your web browser stores in order to simplify future interactions with a particular website. This information is only used by us to improve the navigation and content of the website.

If you wish to stop “cookie” information about yourself from being transmitted, you can turn off this function on your web browser. Please view the “Help” section of your particular web browser to learn how to alter these settings. Keep in mind that turning off cookies might affect the function of the website or prevent you from accessing certain features of the site.

We also collect personal information which is voluntarily given by out visitors, including contact information, e-mail addresses, comments and Zip code. Giving this information is optional.

Email Addresses

We promise that we will only collect names and email addresses which you have voluntarily supplied to us. We use this information only to distribute newsletters and other similar information and we will never share your contact information with an outside party.

When we collect your email address and other personal information, we will use this information to deliver you with relevant content, advertising, services, features and any other information that you request. When you supply us with your email address, we might send you emails related to our services or your activity on the website. We might also contact you regarding new services, changes to our website, new features and any other updates that you might find valuable.

Any personal contact information that you supply us with will be used to optimize your experience and improve the quality of your interaction with The Top Coupon.

You are not required to provide your email address in order to browse our website. If you have submitted your address in the past and you wish to stop receiving our promotional emails, you can email (Insert Unsubscribe Email Here) and we will immediately remove your email address from our contact list.

If The Top Coupon is acquired by another company, your contact information will be passed along to the new owner but will still remain subject to these terms outlined under this privacy policy or any other set of future terms as long as you agree to them.

When You Leave This Website

While browsing The Top Coupon you will find links to other external website which are not controlled by our company, such as sponsors, partners, advertisers and merchants. Please keep in mind that when you leave The Top Coupon and visit these other website you will be subject to their privacy policy. It is recommended that you review the privacy policy of these websites as well because it may be different than ours. We accept no responsibility for the different privacy policies of websites which are not under our ownership or control. 

Sharing Information with Third Parties

We might share your aggregated information about user patterns, habits and characteristics with third parties such as advertisers on your site. This information is anonymous and will not include your personal contact information. We might also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our services and to enhance the website.

We will only share personal contact information volunteered by our users with third parties if we are required to do so by law, if we are required to do so to enforce our Terms and Conditions or if it is required in order to protect our website, property or trademarks.

Visitors Under the Age of 13

This site is not intended to be used by anyone under the age of 13 and no person under 13 should disclose any email addresses or personal information on this website. We promise that we will not knowingly obtain personal information from a child under the age of 13. If someone under the age of 13 has provided their personal contact information to this website without guardian consent, the parent or guardian may contact us to have the information removed. 

Financial Information

We do not collect financial information from our users. If you make a financial transaction it is strictly between yourself and the merchant who you are buying goods or services from. The Top Coupon is not responsible for any financial information which you provide with third party websites. Before providing these third parties with your personal financial information it is recommended that you review their privacy policies. 

Changes to the Privacy Policy

Please be aware that The Top Coupon has the right to alter our privacy policy at anytime with providing notice to its customers. Any changes will be immediately posted on this page and will be effective immediately. 

Contact Information

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or anything else on our website, please don’t hesitate to contact us. The Top Coupon is owned and operated by (Insert the Company Name Here) and the administrator can be reached at this email: (Insert Contact Email Here). We will do our best to respond to all email inquiries within 48 hours.
